this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
this is exciting can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line to the new world
separated from the rest of the straw hat crew luffy is headed to navy headquarters to rescue
his brother ace meanwhile with ace's looming execution only a few hours away the white beard pirates
suddenly appear at navy hq we've got plenty to talk about like you not killing my son father
in an instant the silence is broken and all-out war erupts what the that's not right here comes the
final payoff that harmless sea quake he threatened us with earlier was just the prelude to a massive tsunami
it's a tsunami
ice age
huh you're gonna grace them with your sword for once
i'm just gauging the distance how far do you think he is
strange but somehow it feels like he's standing right in front of us
an all-consuming inferno admiral acaenu's power
urging an all-using波 on SAFE
HUANG
That's insane!
He blocked the world's greatest swordsman?
No, it...it's him!
Third Division Commander Diamond Josu!
Third Division Commander
Third Division ver matin
Third qui
Third Division cai
Third Division damage
Third Division
Sir!
My, my.
Whitebeard's commanders are a frightening bunch of monsters, aren't they?
Though I do admit they put on a good show.
Still, if we want to stop this party before they wreck the place,
we simply need to remove the head of this unruly behemoth.
It's so bright!
What the hell?
Ah! It's Kizaru!
Yasukani's sacred jewel!
It's too bright. Could you tone it down a little, pal?
Could you tone it down a little, pal?
Hmm?
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm.
He just stopped the Admiral's attack, but how?
I don't know!
It's almost like he's got wings!
Huh?
We'll fancy that.
The king's off-limits.
If you want to reach him, you gotta go through me first.
Scary.
These whitebeards play rough.
What the? He's on fire!
He took Kizaru's attack head on, and he's just floating there!
I don't know what kind of devil fruit that is, but I don't like it!
Even more rare than Logia powers.
Zohan type.
Mythical creatures.
I don't know what kind of devil fruit that is, but I don't like it!
Look!
Look! His wounds are healing!
This can't be real.
That didn't work.
I don't know what kind of devil fruit that is, but I don't like it!
What the?
He's on fire!
He took Kizaru's attack head on, and he's just floating there!
I don't know what kind of devil fruit that is, but I don't like it!
Even more rare than Logia powers.
Zohan type.
Mythical creatures.
Look!
His wounds are healing!
This can't be real.
That didn't hurt him at all?
Oh, it did.
Don't lie to protect my pride.
So that must be the first division commander.
If his flames can't turn away an attack, then they can heal him when it's done.
Marco the Phoenix!
Look at that lovely bird.
It must be quite rare.
Well, that's quite the painful kick.
Now you're lying!
Ah!
Ah-
Just standing here is dangerous enough!
He okay?
No! He okay?
Kidaru!
Hmm, my fault.
I really should have known better.
If your boss was that easy to kill,
you wouldn't be here right now, would you?
Huh?
Hey, giant unit,
keep an eye on the sky from now on.
Oh, crap, here come the giants.
Everyone knock them down!
Attack their feet!
Out of the way!
Clear a path!
Shouzou!
Is he breaking the ice?
Okay, retreat!
What the hell is he doing?
Try bucking this one!
It's going to crush us!
We can't outrun it!
I'm trying to run it!
What the hell is he doing?
Uhhhhhh!
I'm dry bucking this one!
It's gonna crush us!
We can't outrun it!
Oh, my God.
What were they thinking abandoning their post like that?
What if I had done the same, huh?
There'd be no one here to do their job.
It's Akainu!
Great Eruption!
The good girl!
He didn't just crush that block of ice.
He evaporated it right into thin air.
Run away!
Volcanic runs!
There's too many of them!
Run, damn it!
The ship has been hit!
Everyone, back away!
I feel like we're watching the apocalypse unfold here.
Sure like to be flashy, don't they?
Think I'll have you light the candles for my next birthday, you magma punk?
I'd rather provide the lighting for your funeral.
How about it, old man?
Still three ships left!
Don't fall back!
Now fire!
PUSH ON!
Get to the plaza!
Good, good, get to the plaza!
Take out the commanders at all costs!
Don't let him get ashore!
Seek the Moby Dick! Push forward and aim for Whitebeard!
These are pirates, my enemy!
This isn't a training exercise, this is war!
I can't!
My knees are frozen, I can't move!
It's pointless.
These guys would slaughter us without a second glance!
I mean, you realize that, right?
Just look around you, there are monsters, vultures!
There's not a single thing amateurs like us can do against guys like that!
We've got to run if we want to live, okay?
Okay?
But…
Look, don't be an idiot!
There is no but, do you understand me?
The only thing we can contribute to this battle is more blood for those killers to spill over the ice!
Just listen! You want to become an admiral, don't you?
Because I promised myself that I'll keep trying… till… till I become a marine admiral!
You said you're gonna fight me, right? Then you will become that strong! You'll have to!
Hey, look! Don't take this the wrong way! I'm just saying! That's why we should run! We both have a future! It's not right for either of us to die here!
There's too much left for us to do! We're the chosen ones!
But… Luffy… I made a promise to him, didn't I?
What now? Where is it?
Here he comes!
There's also kind of feelingsbued shops with the two victims!
I'mить!
Hey, look!
As per hai!
Attack! Kill it!
Alright, break down their artillery defense!
Brutters!
Nicely done! Get him, Little Orse Junior!
He must be related to the continent, Buller.
He's enormous. At least twice as big as one of the regular giants.
We can't let him invade the island, no matter what.
He'll give them too much leverage in the fight.
Seriously?
Just look at that beautiful beast.
And I didn't even know that Orse had a living descendant.
I want it.
I call his corpse after the battle!
Now that's more like it.
Little Orse!
Ace is a nice guy. He's my friend.
I'm not gonna let you hurt him! He won't die!
Although the Straw Hat crew's battle with Orse is long in the past,
Little Orse Junior is still wreaking havoc as a member of Whitebeard's crew.
Bursting through the bay, he goes head to head with the Navy's team of giants
in an earth-shaking confrontation.
On the next, One Piece!
A descendant of the beast!
Little Orse Junior full speed ahead!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Onceία!
I should not catch that!
Until next.
Outside, H